A Guide to the Papers of James J. Kilpatrick
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series I: Correspondence
  - 1953 -1966 Correspondence - Fre (Box-folder 18:2)
    Mrs. A.W.T. Freakes (Kay Patricia Fleming), Fred L. Frechette, Lorene Frederick-Tri-Cities Publishing Company, Mrs. Philip Frederick - Richmond Symphony Orchestra, Richard Frederick, Freedom Academy, Freedom Club, Freedom House, Freedom Press, Freedom's Foundation (Valley Forge), The Freeman, Donald Freeman, G. Mallory Freeman, Jack M. Freeman, Joseph F. Freeman III -Randolph Macon Women's College, L.O. Freeman Jr., Neal B. Freeman, Tanner H. Freeman, Wayne Freeman- The Greenville News, M.J. French, Minerva French, Ralph Freud-University of California Los Angeles (UCLA), Martha P. Freund, Richard H. Frey-Hotel Delido
  - 1956-1967 Correspondence: Fri-end "F" (Box-folder 18:3)
    Friant Dam, Guy Friddell, Dan J. Friedman-Friedman-Marks Clothing, Howard J. Friedman-Florida State Department of Education, Murray Friedman-Anti- Defamation League, H. Clay Friedrichs, David E. Frierson, R.S. Fries-Robertshaw Controls Company/ Black-eyed Pea Society, Carl B. Fritsche, A.B. Fritz, Alton Frix-Lee-Jackson Camp -Sons of Confederate Veterans, Arthur M. Frock, Freeman S. Frost - The Newport Miner, Marcellus B. Frost, Del. Tom Frost, Frostwood American Opinion Bookstore, Chas R. Frutig-Ohio State University Young Republican Club, C.R. and Margaret R. Fry, H.R. Frye, A.J. Fryhoff, Douglas Fugate - Department of Highways, Tom D. Fulford-Virginia Electric and Power Company, Bessie Fuller, Frank H. Fuller-Associated Press, George W. Fuller, Helen Fuller- The New Republic, Henry P. Fuller Sr., Mrs. M.N. Fuller, Selma Fuller, Glenn E. Fulmer, Robert A. Fulwiler Jr., Harry L. Fuqua, Gov. Foster Furcolo, J. Futch-Johns Hopkins University, Shirley E. Futrell
  - 1954-1966 Correspondence: G - Gan (Box-folder 18:4)
    Mr. Gahan, Beverly Gaines, Dr. Francis Pendleton Gaines- Washington and Lee University, Dr. F.P. Gaines Jr.-University of Arizona, Wilfred Galbraith- Anniston Star, Robert L. Gale- Equal Employment Opportunity Commission, Walter S. Galeski- American Council for Judaism, Father Conan Gallagher- Holy Trinity Mission Seminary, Mrs. Frank Marion Galleher, Gallery of Modern Art, Mrs. R.W. Gallonay, Walter R. Gambill, G. Alvan Gamble, Harry Pollard Gamble Sr.-Gamble and Gamble, Jerry Gammon- Reynolds Metal Company, Robertshaw-Fulton Controls Company, John Gange- University of Virginia Woodrow Wilson Department of Foreign Affairs, D.M. Ganly- New York Herald Tribune, Walter W. Gann, William H. Gannett- Rochester Convention and Publicity Buearu Inc., Horace B. Gans- Better Business Bureau, Mrs. A.M. Gant, O.D. Ganton, ___ Ganz, Albert G. Ganz
  - 1953-1966 Correspondence: Gar (Box-folder 18:5)
    James Gardner- Music Minus One, F. Henry Garber, Mrs. Henry Pelham Garber, Honorable Henry Garber, Marshall Garber- Virginia State Chamber of Congress, Dr. R.D. Garcin Jr., Mrs. Edwina Glenn Garfield, Charles Garian, Norbert F. Gariety, R.C. Garland, Charles L. Garnett, Mrs. Theodore Stanford Garnett, W.E. Garnett, G. Edmond Massie- Garrett and Massie, Inc., B.C. Garrett Jr., George Garrett- University of Virginia English Department, Henry E. Garrett- University of Virginia Education, Mrs. James E. Garrett, Judy Garrett, Peggy Tant, and Betty Lou Guidt, Jacqueline Garris, Devin A. Garrity- Devin-Adair Company, C.O. Garshwiler- Educational News Service, John L. Garson, Thomas J. Gartland- Arabian American Oil Company, Richard C. Garvey- Springfield Daily News, Earnest D. Gary, J. Vaughan Gary- United States House of Representatives Committee on Appropriations
  - 1956-1965 Correspondence: Gas - Gat (Box-folder 18:6)
    Honorable J. Ralph Gasque, Hans E. Gassman, Robbins L. Gates, Spencer Gates, Marian Gatterman
  - 1953-1966 Correspondence: Gau - Gen (Box-folder 19:1)
    William M. Gaunt Jr.-Virginia Chain Store Council, Mrs. C.W. Gauntlett, Berian O. Gause, Arnold Gavell, Elbert E. Gray, Thomas B. Gay, William T. Gay, J.J. Gayden Jr.-Hill Directory Company, Inc., Michael Gayle, E.K. Gaylord- The Daily Oklahoman, W.H. Gayman- Jet Propulsion Laboratory, Jeffrey B. Gayner- Conservative Society of Washington and Lee, Mrs. E.W. Gearles, James J. Geary- Virginia Civil War Commission, Vernon M. Geddy Jr.-Golden Horseshoe Club, Edward F. Gee- State-Planters Bank of Commerce and Trusts, Mary Gee- Commission on Constitutional Government, Mrs. R.C. Gee, Milt Geis, Betty Gelb- Virginia Education Fund, Matthew I. Gelfand MD, J.G. Gellings, Daryl Gemmer, Henry Gemmill- Chief of Correspondents- Wall Street Journal, William P. Gempp, General Dynamics, General Electric Company, General Features Corporation, J. Geneson, C.R. Gentry- Virginia Department of Welfare and Institutions, Mrs. Elwood M. Gentry, James W. Gentry Jr., S.L. Gentry
  - 1953-1966 Correspondence: Geo - Gile (Box-folder 19:2)
    Katherine F. George- Martinsville and Henry County Mental Health Society, W. Brooks George- Larus and Brother Company, Ray Ger, Kay Ger- Ger Hotel, Martha Gerachis, Emmetta Germaine, Melvin E. German- Taxaid Company, Grace Gerren, C.J. Geyer, Maude J. Geyer, Duncan C. Gibb- Warren County Educational Foundation, Elizabeth Gibble- Volunteer Service Bureau, Hunter M. Gibbons, Mrs. J.S. Gibbs, Dr. John William Gibbs, Lula Gibbs, Mrs. Marion D. Gibbs, Mary R. Gibbs, R.C. Gibbs- Richmond Community Hospital, Stephen W. Gibbs, Mrs. Thomas F. Gibbs, Clare Gibson- George B. Thornhill Co. Inc., Edmund A. Gibson, Edward Gibson, George D. Gibson, J.C. Gibson- Atchison, Topeka, and Santa Fe Railways, Josephine Gibson, Rob[?] F. Gibson, Mrs. Ross S. Gibson, Wilbur F. Gibson, Lawrence E. Gichner, Howard A. Giddings- Giddings & Co., H.E. Gietzen- Travelers Insurance Company, J.G. Gifford, Lewis D. Gilbert- Investor, Rose Gilbert- American Association of Museums, Frank B. Gilbreth- Charleston Evening Post, J.W. Stuart Gilchrist- Children's Home Society of Virginia, A.T. Giles, Egbert Leigh Giles
  - 1956-1966 Correspondence: Gill - Gilma (Box-folder 19:3)
    E. Hobson Gill, George Gill- Louisville Courier Journal, H.B. Gill- Gill Electric Manufacturing Company, H.B. Gill Jr., Katie Gill, Leona Gill, Rita Gill, Virgil H. Gill- Remlik Hall Turkey Farm, Dr. James T. Gillespie, Charles Edgar Gilliam, Christine Smith Gilliam, E.F. Gilliam- Pretlow Peanut Company, Mary Meacham Giliam- Richmond Public Library, Josephine K. Gillikin, James H. Gillis- City Hall Reporter, New Orleans Times Picayune, Norman B. Gillis Jr., Richard S. Gillis Jr.-Virginia State Chamber of Congress, W.H. Gilman, Gene F. Gilmartin- The Rotunda Club, Gene Gilmartine- Cleveland Yachting Club Inc.
  - 1953-1957 Correspondence: Howard C. Gilmer Jr. (Box-folder 19:4)
  - 1956-1966 Correspondence: W.B. Gilmer -Gl (Box-folder 19:5)
    W.B. Gilmer, Catherine Lee Gilsdorf, Ann Ginalski, Daniel L. Ginsberg, Ginter Park Woman's Club Yearbook, Gordon Gipson- Caxton Printers Ltd., J.H. Gipson Sr.-Caxton Printers Ltd., Girl Scouts of USA, Beverly Githens, Lewis Glaser, Milton Glaser, C.S. Glasgow, Carter Glass III- The News and Advance, J. Luther Class- Department of Welfare and Institutions, Robert V. Glazebrook, Powell Glass Jr. -Glass Publishing Company, Charles W. Glenn- Motley Construction Company Inc., Marjorie P. Glenn, Mary B. Glenn, Harry Glidden, William R. Glidden, Emmet Glore, Admiral R.O. Glover- Atlantic Rural Exposition, Fiorella Maxwell Glowe
  - 1953-1966 Correspondence: Go - Gol (Box-folder 19:6)
    Harvie D. Goddin Jr., Mrs. F. Russell Godie, Mrs. Julian C. Godsey Sr., Senator Mills E. Godwin Jr., Dr. Winfred Godwin, C.M. Goethe, Ray Goetz, Oliver Kenneth Goff, F.E. Goggin, Kenneth Goit (?), Mary Lou Goin, Victor Gold, Sid Goldberg- North American Newspaper Alliance Inc., Ariel L. Goldburg, Allan Golden, Harry Golden- The Carolina Israelite, Golden Horseshoe Club, Major Marvin L. Golden- Fitzsimons Army Hospital, T.T. Golden, Ronald L. Goldfarb, M.T. Golding- Community Welfare Committee, Eric F. Goldman- Princeton University, Paul A. Goldman- Lieutenant United States Air Force, Robert Goldman, Ed Goldstein, Barry Goldwater, Goldwater Column, Robert A. Goldwin- Public Affairs University of Chicago
  - 1954-1965 Correspondence: Gon - Gor (Box-folder 20:1)
    Henry R. Gonner- Central Richmond Association Inc., W.E. Gonter, Donald J. Gonzales, Martee Gooch, R.K. Gooch, Mrs. Rugby R. Goode, W.B. Goode, Mrs. B. Goodman, Julian Goodman- National Broadcasting Company, M.M. Goodman, Robert C. Goodman Jr.- Collegiate Schools, Ernest W. Goodrich, Mrs. W.R. Goodson, Reverend Conrad H. Goodwin Sr.- Christ Church Rectory, John M. Goodwin, Richard Goodwin, John C. Goolrick, Mrs. Adelaide Rawls Goolsby, Oscar W. Goolsby, G.W. Gordner Jr., Daniel N. Gordon- University of Wisconsin, Gertrude H. Gordon, Howard H. Gordon-Southern States Cooperative Inc., Howard K. Gordon, John M. Gordon, Mary Stuart Gordon, Robert L. Gordon - The San Marcos Hotel and Bungalows, Rosalie M. Gordon, Dr. Samuel G. Gordon, Tom Gordon, W.W. Gordon-Chesterfield County Public Schools, Honorable Albert Gore-U.S. Senate Committee on Rules and Administration, Lillian L. Gore-Department of Health, Education, and Welfare, A.B. Gorman, Walter P. Gorman Jr., Dick Gorrell, J.E. Gorski
  - 1953-1967 Correspondence: Gos - Grava (Box-folder 20:2)
    Betty A. Goscin, John A. Gosnell-National Small Business Association, Howard Gossage, Judge James P. Gossett, Bill Gottlieb - American Council for Judaism, Alan J. Gould- Associated Press, Bernard Gould, Richard S. Gould - Emco Inv. Co., A.T. Goulding-Standard Public Relations, Mrs. George S. Gouldman, Muriel Nussey Gouldman, Mr. and Mrs. Robert Goulet, Government Printing Office, Governor's Office, Mrs. Perrin W. Gower Sr. T. Charles Gower, William Grad-RESPONSE Symposium, Ed Grade- Los Angeles Times Syndicate, Edith C. Grady, George Graham, J. Stuart Graham Jr., Louise Graham, Malcolm C. Graham, Mrs. R.D. Graham, Lady Susan Graham, Grand Rapids -Planning Director, Bert J. Grant, Charles Grant, Grover C. Grant, Hugh G. Grant, Mrs. Arthur Granthary (?), Edward M. Grapp, Joyce D. Gratz, Alma Gravatt, J. Segar Gravatt, Mr. John B. Gravatt, Mrs. John Bryan Gravatt, Jr., W. Moncure Gravatt
  - 1953-1966 Correspondence: Grave - Graz (Box-folder 20:3)
    John O.W. Gravely III- Virginia Gazette, Jemie Lee Graves, John Temple Graves- Birmingham Post Herald, L.R. Graves, Mrs. Carroll Gray, Elmon T. Gray, Frederick T. Gray, Garland Gray- Virginia State Senator, Grayfred B. Gray, Miss M. Frances Gray, Marvin L. Gray- Ruritan National, Mrs. Marvin L. Gray- Tidewater Academy, Maud Merchant Gray, P.M. Gray, Mrs. Wilmer L. Gray, Judge L.A. Grayson- Criminal Court of Record, Alfred de Grazia- New York University
  - 1956-1966 Correspondence: Gre - Gree (Box-folder 20:4)
    Greater Philadelphia Magazine, Elmore D. Greaves, Ashbel Green- Alfred A. Knopf Inc., Mrs. Calvin S. Green, Mrs. D.E. Green, E.A. Green, Mrs. Ebert Green, Mrs. Etta Green, Dr. George Preston Green, Gerald Green- Boston University, H. Bruce Green, Herman C. Green, Milton L. Green, Montgomery M. Green, Patricia K. Green- Weber Showcase and Fixture Company, Mrs. Ralph E. Green, Walter G. Green, Mrs. Sam Greenberg, A.C. Greene Jr.-Louisa County Education Association, Burnley C. Greene, Judge John D. Greene, Marc T. Greene- Providence Journal, Richard T. Greene, Miss Erna Greenebaum, Ted Greenleaf- Public Relations Director DePaul University, Sidney Greenstein, Irving S. Greentree Jr.
  - 1956-1966 Correspondence: Greg - Grey (Box-folder 20:5)
    A. James Gregor- International Association for Advancement of Ethnology and Eugenics, Alessandro Gregorian, Claiborne D. Gregory- Virginia Petroleum Industries Comm., Mrs. Earle D. Gregory, Mrs. Irma Miller Gregory, Mrs. Jettie B. Gregory, Lewis W. Gregory, Margaret K. Gregory- The Hotel Jefferson, Mrs. Quentin Gregory, Ralph N. Gregory- South Carolina State Chamber of Commerce, J. Willard Greer, T. Keister Greer, Robert C. Gresham- Council of State Chambers of Commerce, William F.S. Gresham- Equitable Life Assurance Society, J.V. Grey, Robert J. Grey
  - 1956-1966 Correspondence: Gri - Grin (Box-folder 20:6)
    Evelyn Field Griffin- Woman's Club of Wakefield, Commander H.K. Griffin Jr.-U.S. Atlantic Fleet, John A. Griffin- Emory University, L. Francis Griffin- First Baptist Church, Lloyd Griffin- North Carolina Citizens Association, Martin .J. Griffin, Governor Samuel Marvin Griffin (Georgia), Richard W. Griffin, Robert P. Griffin- U.S. Senate, Stuart Griffin- Foreign Correspondents Club of Japan, George D. Griffith Jr.-Southside Insurance Association, Luther O. Griffith- Griffith Lumber Company, W.J. Griffith- The Palladium Item, H.J. Griffiths, Austin E. Grigg, Wilbur W. Griggs, Mrs. Ben M. Grimes, J.E. Grimsley-Richmond Newspaper Guild, Doris Grinstead
  - 1958-1966 Correspondence: Gris - Gry (Box-folder 21:1)
    Dean Erwin N. Griswold- Harvard University, Desdemona Griswold (Francis F.), Mrs. Ralph E. Griswold, Roger Groce, Dean G. Grogan- Blue Cross Blue Shield, H.W. Gross, Gerald M. Grosshans, Lilian T. Grosshans, William Groth- Safety, Health, Welfare Building, J. Bryan Grubbs, Joseph H. Grubbs Jr.-Title Insurance and Trust Company, Mrs. Joseph Grubbs Jr., A.K. Grube- Southside Plaza Shopping Center, Victor Gruen, Ernest Gruening- U.S. Senate, Grump Inc., Lois Ann Grunow, Ted W. Grunst, Richard Gryziec
  - 1956-1967 Correspondence: Gu - Gw (Box-folder 21:2)
    Dr. DuPont Guerry III, C.D. Guess- Southern Teachers Agency of Richmond, Honorable Raymond R. Guest, Harry F. Guggenheim- Newsday, June Purcell Guild, William J. Guilfoile- New York Yankees Inc., James Dudley Gullet, G.W. Gulmon, Beth Gundlach, Edward R. Gunn. Richard E. Gunn- Liller Neal Battle & Lindsey Inc., Evelyn W. Gunter, Mrs. J.P. Gunter, Irene E. Gunther, Edward J. Gurney- U.S. House of Representatives, Joe Gusky- Lando Advertising Agency Inc., Dr. Hilmer C.H. Gustavson, Richard W. Guthrie, Mrs. V.V. Gutshall, G. Christian Guvernator III, Jean Guyton- University of Mississippi, Mrs. John H. Gwathmey, Robert R. Gwathmey- Hanover County Jamestown Festival Committee Inc., Pamela Denyce Gwathney
  - 1953-1967 Correspondence: Ha - Had (Box-folder 21:3)
    Henrietta H__., Richard W. Haase, Rose Habel, Robert J. Habenicht- A.H. Robins Company, Inc., C.P. Haber, Mohamed Habib- Embassy of Egypt in Washington D.C., Charles Haboush, Edward E. Haddock MD- Mayor of Richmond, M.C. Haddon-Lockheed Aircraft Corporation, T. Gray Haddon- Assistant Commonwealth's Attorney
  - 1956-1963 Correspondence: Joseph Addison Hagan and Mrs. J. Addison Hagan (Box-folder 21:4)
  - 1957-1966 Correspondence: Hage - Hair (Box-folder 21:5)
    Mrs. E.B. Hagenmueller, Randall Hagner, V.W. Hague, T. Marshall Hahn Jr.-Virginia Polytechnic Institute, Mrs. Jerre Haigh- Stephens College Office of Development, Elster M. Haile, Rochelle Haimes, Esther H. Haines, Mr. and Mrs. Forrest L. Haines, James J. Haire- Howard F. Dugan Inc.
  - 1956-1966 Correspondence: Fred Haislip- Logan County Taxpayer's Association of West Virginia (Box-folder 21:6)
  - 1953-1966 Correspondence: Haiz - Hall (Box-folder 21:7)
    Margaret Haizlip, William F. Halcomb- Southeast Missouri State College, H. Halderson, Donne Hale- Fitness and Figure, E.V. Hale, J. Evetts Haley, Laura Virginia Hale, Doug Hall, National Jefferson Davis Hall of Fame Committee, Grover C. Hall Jr.-Montgomery Advertiser, James K. Hall Jr., Ralph A. Hall, Mrs. Raymond C. Hall- Hall-Neale Inc. Advertising, Hall Syndicate Inc., W. Earl Hall- Mason City Globe Gazette, Mrs. W.J.B. Hall
  - 1955-1966 Correspondence: Halle - Hamm (Box-folder 22:1)
    William C. Halley- Du Pont Magazine, Andrew Halpin, Ashley Halsey Jr.-University of South Carolina, The American Rifleman, E.K. Halsey, Robert J. Halstead, Milton S. Hamacher, Newman Hamblet- Thalhimer Brothers Inc., L.A. Hamel- Beech-Nut Life Savers Inc., C.H. Hamilton, Mrs. Erwin Hamilton, Grace Hamilton, Jack Hamilton- Northern Virginia Daily (John A.) Lynchburg Advance, Norfolk Ledger-Star, Jack Hamilton- Detroit Free Press, Lt. Larry Hamilton- Public Information Office, O.F. Hamilton Jr.-Hamilton Manufacturing Company, R.H. Hamilton, Ray V. Hamilton, W.N. Hamilton, John Hamlin, William S. Hamma, W.K. Hammaker- Tidewater Oil Company, Earl L. Hammond, Nancy J. Hammond, William Hammond
  - 1953-1966 Correspondence: Hamo - Harc (Box-folder 22:2)
    Sidney L. Hamolsky- Brown University, Gray Hampton Jr.- Buffalo Presbyterian Church, J. Nat Hamrick Jr., Joseph G. Hamrick- Virginia Governor's Office, Division of Industrial Development and Planning, Blanton B. Hanbury- Buffalo Shook Company Inc., Prince Edward Educational Foundation, Dr. Gordon B. Hancock, J.E. Hancock- Henrico County Tuberculosis Association, Leigh Hanes, Thomas A. Hanes- Sigma Delta Chi- Tidewater Virginia Chapter, Hanigen-Wick Memorial Fund, Florence P. Hanisch, Richard P. Hankins, John T. Hanna- City Traffic Engineer- Richmond, W. Clark Hanna, Cora W. Hannah, Mrs. W.N. Hannah, Reverend John P. Hannan, Hanover Academy 2 nd grade class, Nina Hansen, William E. Hansen- Young Men's Christian Association, Arthur B. Hanson, Daniel P. Hanson- Connecticut Mutual Life Insurance Company, Florence E. Hanson, Chuck Harbaugh-Chamber of Commerce of United States, E.L. Harcastle
  - 1956-1967 Correspondence: Hard - Harre (Box-folder 22:3)
    Mrs. Romaine Hardcastle- Sitka, Alaska Chamber of Commerce, Gertrude Hardeman, Mrs. Isaac Hardeman, Richard Hardesty Jr.- R.H. Hardesty Company Inc., Hardesty Candy Company, Garland S. Hardin, Mrs. Franklin L. Harding, John Howard Harding, Mrs. S.Y. Harding, E.V. Hardway Jr., Mrs. J.C. Hardy, Congressman Porter Hardy Jr.-House Office Building, Billy James Hargis- Christian Crusade, William J. Hargis Jr.-Laboratory Director and Dean School of Marine Science, Roy B. Hargrove Jr.-Prince Edward School Foundation, James E. Hargroves, S.A. Harkness, D.A. Harley, Bryce N. Harlow- The White House, Lansing B. Harmon Jr., Mrs. John Harner, Joseph M. Harp- The Herald- Mail Company, Bob Harper, R.M. Harper, Rita P. Harper- The Reader's Digest, Walter W. Harper- State Development Board, State of South Carolina, Harper's Magazine, F. Stanley Harrell, George V. Harrell Jr., Herbert H. Harrell, Richard O. Harrell III, Ted Harrell
  - 1954-1963 Correspondence: Anthony Harrigan- Norfolk-Virginian Pilot, The News and Courier: Charleston Evening Post (Box-folder 22:4)
  - 1953-1966 Correspondence: H.Harrigan - A. Harrison (Box-folder 22:5)
    Herbert Harrigan, C. Herbert Harrigan Jr., Charlotte J. Harris, Edwin F. Harris, Frank D. Harris- Hodges and Harris, G.C. Harris, George Carleton Harris, Gibson Harris, H.H. Harris- Department of Highways, Jane M. Harris- Fall Mountain Regional High School Librarian, Janie Harris, Juliette L. Harris, Logan Harris, Mildred Willis Harris, Roy V. Harris- Southern Finance Building, Sidney J. Harris- General Features Corporation, Chicago Daily News, Violet Harris, W. Gibson Harris, William Harris, A.S. Harrison Jr.-Governor of Virginia, Arthur W. Harrison- C&P Telephone Company of Virginia, Friends of the Library
  - 1952-1963 Correspondence: Burr P. Harrison- House of Representatives, U.S. Congress (Box-folder 22:6)
  - 1953-1967 Correspondence: C. Harrison -Harw (Box-folder 22:7)
    Mrs. Channing Williams Harrison, D.F. Harrison, Eve Harrison, Mrs. Milton W. Harrison- Stan-Hywet Hall, Mr. and Mrs. Walter M. Harrison- The North Star, The Traveler's Insurance Company, William P. Harrison, Willis S. Harrison- National Conference of Editorial Writers, Deryl Hart- President Duke University, George L. Hart Jr.-District of Columbia U.S. District Court Judge, Hazel Marr Hart, James Hart, Merwin K. Hart- National Economy Council Inc., W. Robert Hart, The Hartford Times, Lille May Hartless, Ben R. Hartley- Presbyterian Survey, Fred A. Hartley Jr., Herbert L. Hartley MD- Northwest Medicine, Honorable William B. Hartsfield- Atlanta, Georgia mayor, Samuel T. Hartt, James Hartz, Clarence L. Harvey, Irene Harvey, Iva C. Harvey, Keith Harvey- The Bedford Bulletin, Richard B. Harwell- Association of College and Research Libraries, Elizabeth Harwood, Garland M. Harwood Jr.
  - 1953-1966 Correspondence: Has - Haz (Box-folder 23:1)
    Fred Haseltine- Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, Douglas Haskell- Architecture FORUM, Preston Hampton Haskell, C.N. Hastie Jr.-Magnolia Gardens, Dr. Martin Hasting- St. Louis University, Cathy Hastings, Paul D. Hastings, Woodrow W. Hasty- River Road Church, Elizabeth F. Haswell, John Davis Hatch Jr. -Norfolk Museum of Arts and Sciences, Honorable W. Russell Hatchett, Weston P. Hatfield, R.B. Hathaway- Yale Club, H. Hatton, Hartwell Hatton- Pulpwood Production, Hatton, Brown, and Company Inc. Publishers, Cynthia Haug, Dr. Ernst Hauswedell, R.B. Hawes, E. Beverly Hawkins, Herman Bruce Hawkins, Lucy Rogers Hawkins, Nettie and Ben Hawkins, Thomas Lee Hawley- The Virginia Spectator, Mrs. C. Haws, R.A. Hay, Alice Hayes, Charles R. Hayes, Daniel R. Hayes- Hanover House, Lillian L. Haynes, Sam Haynes, W.P. Hazlegrove, Henry Hazlitt- The Freeman
  - 1956-1966 Correspondence: He - Hea (Box-folder 23:2)
    Orman L. Headley, Reverend Joseph B. Head, George W. Healy Jr. - Times- Picayune Publishing Company, Peggy Price Heard, Mildred M. Crooks- Richmond Area Heart Association Inc., Mrs. Paul A. Heart, Edwin J. Heath, Hubert H. Heath, William H. Heath- The Haverhill Gazette, The American Editor, Lawrence Eagle Tribune, Mrs. Frances C. Heaton
  - 1957-1966 Correspondence: Heb-James Helmes (Box-folder 23:3)
    Robert Heberle- Richmond City Council, Dr. Hedges, Marvin K. Heffner, Louis P. Hehman- Citizens for Decent Literature, Colonel R.D. Heinl Jr., Heinrich Bar, Ed. Heiny, E.R. Heiser, J.N. Heiskell- Arkansas Gazette, Dr. Joseph D. Heitger, Dr. Edward C. Held, Lewis I. Held, J. Lynn Helms- North American Aviation Inc., James M. Helms Jr.-Longwood College Department of History
  - 1963-1966 Correspondence: Jesse Helms- WRAL TV (Box-folder 23:4)
  - 1953-1966 Correspondence: Helt - Her (Box-folder 23:5)
    Alice D. Helton, Herb Heltzer- Ardley, Beth Hemingway, W. Edwin Hemphill- Virginia Calvacade, Virginia State Library, Albert E. Hemsing- U.S. Information Service, Aubrey R. Henderson Jr., Bernard L. Henderson Jr., Horace Henderson, Jeremiah Henderson, Mrs. W. E. Henderson, John F. Hendon, Captain C.D. Henington- USAF Recruiting Service, Bill Henley, August L. Henna, Louis Hennessy- The Azusa Herald, Alex Henney- English Speaking Union, Mrs. J.R. Henning- Brunswick-Greensville Regional Library, Joyce Henriques, J. Henkel Henry- Henry Sub-Division, Paul W. Henry, Mrs. E.E. Hensley, George Henton, Lt. Col. Guy Hepler- Salvation Army, The Herald Tribune News Service, R.B. Herbert, Charles F. Herd- Greater Knoxville Chamber of Commerce, Marion W. Herget- Herald Progress Inc., John W. Herman, Mrs. William C. Herman, A.B. Hermann- Republican National Committee, Milton M. Hermanson, Booton Herndon, Louis S. Herrink, Ruth Herrink, Grady C. Herron- Human Events Inc.
  - 1956-1967 Correspondence: Hes - Hey (Box-folder 23:6)
    Joan Hess- The American Artists, Karl Hess- The Fisherman, Champion Paper and Fibre Company, Laura E. Hesse, Mrs. George P. Hester, Sue S. Hester- Board of Education Methodist Church, Harvey H. Hevenor, Mrs. O.H. Hewit Jr., Horace W. Hewlett- Amherst College, Mrs. Owen Heyer
  - 1953-1966 Correspondence: Hi - Hill (Box-folder 23:7)